Hello, can you hear me?
First, let's import our model.
Since the waist of our model is wider than that of our model,
we changed its waist size to import our sample paper.
After the sample paper is imported,
we will set all the symmetrical panels to be left and right symmetrical.
We can open the base line of the sample paper and place it in a position that does not block the model.
Then use our positioning ball to arrange the level of our panel.
The coordinates of this positioning ball are recommended to use our world coordinates.
After arranging the level, we use our arrangement point tool
to quickly
arrange the panel to the corresponding arrangement point of our model.
Then we can adjust its X-axis and Y-axis in the property editor.
Take a look, and then go to the back of our model.
Also arrange it.
Make it a little wider, so that it does not penetrate our model so seriously.
Then the panel of the waist.
Make sure you apply the counterfeit tool to the post.
Right
OK.
Then the piccons of the waist area should be in a parallel position in front of the buckle.
And then it is one of our door doors.
It is a Hamburg belt.
The front door of the hem has two panels.
We can use this quick arrangement tool to move it to the corresponding position of us.
OK
That's the first word.
Look anywhere, I'll show you.
After arranging, we have some small panels, we can arrange them later
You can put it on top first
And then we're going to sew the small panels with our sewing line
Add it directly to the outside and quickly arrange it for him
And then we're going to turn these panels on and off
And then we sew
Anyway, there should be no problem with this part
So today's material is
I can share it with you. When the time comes, this version will include
I'm going to make some of these water-washed patterns and share them with you in our
WeChat keywords and
The link to the Baidu plate below the B station, we will do it in the comments area. You can go and get it next week.
Who's
You
Are
Just sew it together using the internal line
Remember to change the type of the sewing line to our turn
And then because of the panel, he said he didn't want to take it anymore
There is a layer relationship, we use the layer setting tool to set the layer relationship between them
Ensure a stable simulation
Then add the buckle on the waist
We can rotate the direction of the buckle in our attribute editor
Remember the buckle, press the button at the 3D window, then press the button to buckle
This model is a foldable model
So we will teach you how to make a foldable model
Later we will make a foldable model
Because it is much longer than our model, it may not be as convenient if you just turn it over
Shift and Q can be used to hide the version
Let's look at a layer relationship
Now let's make a foldable model
Set an internal cable
Then sew it
Then add it to the outside
Simulate
I forgot to sew the side
Simulate again
Pull it a little
Simulate it
After simulating, delete the sewing line above
In this way, the foldable effect is done
Now we go to our library to find a piece of denim fabric and apply it
Use the fabric you have already used
After using it, we can add it to the fabric we have already used
kle
Turn over the fabric
Forcees
Turn over therin
Turn over the制
Turn over the printed ir T-shirt
Turn over the fabric
Turn over
There is no special point in sewing here, so the speed will be a little faster.
After sewing, we will sew a leather label on the back.
The leather label is made of sheepskin fabric.
Now we will make a double-layer waistband.
This is the waistband.
Because the waistband is made of double layers, it will be more effective.
Because the texture of the fabric on the inside will be different.
The cologne layer comes out.
Now let's take a look at the crotch.
We will make a small fold for it.
Because the fold of the seam allowance can also be made.
We can make it out again.
Expand the outer line of the fabric.
Then make an inner line of the shoulder strap.
Then harden the fabric.
After hardening, we will find our folding arrangement tool in the 3D window.
Fold it.
The folding words are connected on both sides.
The folding angle is manually changed to our zero degree.
Then sew it.
Adjust the sewing line to its length.
Pull it to the bottom.
Okay, simulate it.
Then such a whole crotch fold structure is done.
Improve our clothing quality.
Okay, the panel line of the穩
It's actually a double structure.
And its sewing position will be about 2 mm inside.
There will also be a sewing line.
So we give her a internal line of 2 mm.
Some people say my hand speed is fast, this speed is actually because we don't have a lot of focus on sewing, so I didn't put a lot of focus on sewing.
I put it faster.
We add the thickness of the fabric to the original thickness of the fabric,
so that it can create a double layer effect.
Now let's see how to merge the corners of the fabric.
Because it was originally a pattern, we removed it.
After merging, it is the same effect as the original pattern.
In order to make the folding effect better,
we still hook the base line after merging.
We still hook the base line after merging.
Then set the folding angle,
and delete the inner line of the sewing support line.
Now we need to take you to make a small strip on the side, and this small strip is to simulate the structure of our real sewing edge.
We can measure the length of this small strip, and its width is 5mm, and then sew it on our side.
Remember to change the type of sewing line to our Turn.
Then manually reduce the diameter of the strip and the conflict thickness.
Then add it to the inside, and simulate it.
When the control is sent out, we can simulate the symmetrical strip.
Then we can simulate the symmetrical strip.
We can simulate the symmetrical strip.
Then we turn the Turn into a bullfrog style.
Then we can simulate the symmetrical strip.
Then adjust the width and thickness of the turn.
We can use a golden brown for the color.
We can simulate the symmetrical strip.
You can see that the direction of the eye is not right now, and then turn it around
Select the eye, turn its angle 180 degrees
Turn it over
Then set its width
Adjust the color
Then we have some nail effects on some other small panels
Then we can also do it
This is also a pattern of our twist tool to select a nail
Change the width of our nail
Then add it to the corresponding position of our panel
If you can't see it clearly, you can adjust it to a white texture display
Add again
Then copy to the parallel modified panel, no need to add twice
Change the material
Change the color
Change the position of the line
Change the positions of the line
Eliminate the sorry position
We have done the
Now we need to give our pants the texture of our jeans pants
The texture of jeans pants is a
How can I say that it has a superimposed fabric of the un-watered part,
there are two different textures in front and the back of it,
If we do a water wash on it, there will be a difference in the front and back of the water wash according to different techniques.
As you can see in this picture, I used the microglia water wash and the three types of water wash after the water wash.
Both are different.
When we do it, we need to get some points first.
That is, the process of processing the fabric.
We can choose a larger area of clothing to scan the fabric to avoid some areas where the color is not even.
We have to keep scanning the front and back of both sides because the back effect is different.
If you want to achieve a better result, at least scan 150 to 300 dpi.
Then we can use some third-party software, such as Pixplant and Photoshop, to process some four-sided fabric.
In this process,
I have already talked about it in a previous video.
For some irregular water wash, we can scan the sample as large as possible.
So that the effect is more natural when we do it in four directions.
When necessary, we can use Photoshop to adjust the color of our fabric.
Make the color close to the actual fabric color.
You can see that there is a bad example and a better example below.
This better example will make the water wash effect on the edge of the sample.
We are going to use this pattern, so let's scan it in.
We can see that we can scan it first.
Then we can cut it in the PS.
Then we can remove some bad things and fix it.
Then we can avoid some problems when we do it again.
Then we can make a four-sided pattern of this pattern.
Then we can adjust the color.
To compare the actual effect to get a close-up.
In the case of a sample wash,
For the time of the sample wash,
And some of the water wash techniques we used,
It will have a different color-discreasing effect.
In some way, we can use Photoshop to adjust its color.
to make it darker or brighter.
We can use the image to adjust the colors.
There are some pictures here, let's take a look.
For example, the five texture pictures here
are all adjusted by our second picture.
They are all under the colors.
You can see that there are three small triangles here.
We can adjust the colors through these three triangles
to make it darker or brighter.
Let me adjust the PS.
There will be a Q&A session later.
Let's go through the process first.
Don't worry.
I've already remembered this question.
I'll adjust it for you later.
Let's apply this texture picture to our pants.
This is our front picture.
We've also done the hair line picture.
Remove the small hook at the back
and add the texture picture and hair line picture
to the front picture.
After that, we can see the effect of the fold.
And then we can see whether the pattern
that we created with Cologne
needs to be turned over on the surface
so that it faces inwards.
Now we can see that the overall effect
is already done.
Now let's do the hair line picture.
We've already talked about the hair line picture
in the previous course.
So this part will be faster.
Let's add a hair line picture first.
And then we can see the effect of the hair line picture.
You can find the corresponding hair line picture
in the top stitch of the canvas window.
For example, I found a double-edged hair line picture
and applied it directly.
And then we'll change the thickness of the hair line picture
to be a little thicker.
And then we'll change the color
to the yellow of this copper color.
Adjust the gap between the two hair lines.
And then apply some other positions.
After we've applied all the positions of the double-edged hair line,
we can copy them again.
And then change the double-edged hair line
to a single hair line.
We don't need to try other properties.
And then we can change the name.
The key of this hair line is 1.6.
Let's set it to single 1.6.
And then apply the position of this single hair line.
Like the one on the pants.
Use our line hair line
to add this whole section directly.
Just add it.
And then we'll kimchi this hair line.
All right.
OK, we're going to copy this another one here.
Sales this one hair line at the 0.
And then we can make it fight the ничего about us.
Double-edged hair line
Make him straight on the internal line of our hair.
For bobby hair,
we need an 1.6 style of a highную
So use the top one.
And then the sides...
we need an edge.
And so that we'll create this And then we're going toNA
裤子口袋这个地方的话,我刚刚是直接用了一个双铭线,那其实呢,它在版面上是有一个基础线的,那我们根据这个基础线的效果来做我们的铭线,我们可以将它先勾勒一下。
勾勒好之后呢,我们直接用我们的这个单线系的一个铭线给它做一下。
好,那现在我们来看我们侧缝啊,侧缝的话我们是要做一个包边的一个锁边线剂的一个效果,那首先呢我们先创建一个新的铭线类型,然后选到我们的一个overlock啊,将它的一个网格面改到全部,这样的话它的正面背面都会有一个锁边的一个线剂的效果。
好,那最后呢我们再加一个我们的一个打枣的一个线剂。
打枣线剂。
打枣线剂是我们的这个Bartok啊。
它要直接压在内部线上是不是把它的间距调整为0啊。
颜色也调一下。
好,那现在呢我们所有的铭线呢都已经做好了,那我们就可以将这个不需要有对称关系的位置呢我们去给它先解除掉我们的一个板片的一个对称。
然后呢将不需要铭线的那个地方给它删掉啊。
但是这个功能呢可以给大家预告一下,因为这个地方它确实是不太方便嘛,因为我们有时候这个铭线虽然是不对称的,但它板片的其他地方是对称的。
所以说在我们的6.2的版本当中呢我们的铭线是可以设置为左右不对称了。
大家可以关注一下这个功能啊,新功能到时候也会有直播的。
。
Finally, in the pocket here, we can make a decorative name line
Draw an internal line by yourself
Then apply the name line of our single line
Now let's take a look at our leather label
This leather label, we use the fabric of our default little sheepskin
Then we can use our texture editor tool to make a pattern
Then I will use our CLOUD logo
Directly drag this picture in
We can shrink its size
Then fold the front and back
Then flatten
After flattening, we can put its texture in place
Rotate the direction
Like this
Because it is a flat bottom
So the texture of the leather of the bottom layer can be seen
Then we add the name line
The inner side should also have a name line
We can also add it
Okay, now let's get into the explanation of our water wash effect
It's also today's highlight
Our water wash effect is divided into two parts
The first part is about the water wash effect of our edge
The water wash effect of the edge of the cowhide clothing
A starting effect
It is actually based on the difference between our seam and needle
Its effect is different
Then we can make some repeated use
A common effect
As our own pattern
Then you can see there are four places below
First of all, the side seam
It has no effect when pressing the name line
Then it is the effect of our inner seam
Then it is the effect of the side seam pressing the single needle line
And the effect of our crotch
Including our waist
All can be made into such a water-washed pattern
Then use our sewing wrinkle tool to make an addition
You can see some pictures here
On the left is a picture of our actual sample
On the right is the effect in the cloth
Later we will see its operation in the software
First of all, let's take a look
Let's scan the pattern of the crotch
After scanning
In the PS
Let's take a piece
Can be made into a square continuous area
It is still used as our sewing wrinkle tool
After taking it
Let's create a new layer
Copy a new layer
Then we will remove this new layer
Why do you want to remove the color
In this way, we can better choose its area
After removing the color, adjust the color connection
Let it have the effect of black and white
In this way, when we choose
It is easy to delete unnecessary places
Then use the sewing wrinkle tool to select the area we need to delete
Black and gray
Then delete this texture
Then we add another layer
Fill in the black
Remember to cancel our selection when filling in
Fill in again
Fill in the black
Then we use our filter tool to make the position
Make it a square continuous effect
This square continuous processing
I also talked about it in the previous live class
Use our copy of the picture
Process the position of the seam
Then this
This is our
The edge of the water wash
Then we can take it
The color is also discolored
Then we can adjust the color connection
Adjust the output color connection below
Make it a little bit whiter
Open this black and see the effect
After the effect is OK
We will take this picture
We can cut it
You have to make sure that the bottom of it
Just stick to it
Then
Save this picture
Save it as a png
A pattern pattern
Because it is a transparent
Is it a transparent picture?
Okay, after that
It is
It can be used as our sewing wrinkle
A pattern pattern
Then we find our sewing wrinkle tool
Find our water wash pattern
Then here
There are three pre-made
One is the edge of our pants
Then we can add it in first
The edge of the pants
After adding the pattern of our sewing wrinkle
We
Use this line sewing tool
Add it to the edge of our pants
After adding
We are in the 3D window
You can already see its effect
You can adjust its parameters
After selecting it
Let's take a look at some of its parameters
First of all, it is its width
The default width is 1 cm
Then our pants
Is extended
Not 12 mm
Is 1.2 cm
Then adjust the transparency
What about the effect of this transparency?
We have to open our rendering
To check
What about our water wash effect?
It is due to
In our rendering window
The lighting environment of this 3D window is different
So we have to use the rendering window
The effect of the window
To be accurate
So some of our water wash patterns
Its transparency
This value has to be adjusted
A little lower
The effect will be better
You can switch its material on it
After switching
It is
Because it just
Is a cotton material
It is switched to denim
It is our jeans
After that
Its line drawing
In fact, the effect has changed
So we
Re-add the texture
Adjust the transparency
What about the density?
It refers to
Our water wash
This one
The texture
How to say
That is to say
The larger the value
If it is 100%
If the density is 100%
It is your original
The texture effect
If you adjust it
Is less than 100%
Its density
Will become more dense
Can be understood
Okay, then
We will
On the side
This one
The water wash of the edge
The texture effect
It is also done in the same way
Make it in
Add to our side
One side
Or open the water wash
To confirm its effect
Some people ask
What is the effect of this hair line?
Hair line
In fact, everyone is
Using this sewing needle tool
When
I don't know if you have
I have seen it before
That
A production of Yurongfu
Live broadcast
It is actually
Our hair line
It is doing
Like Yurongfu
That
Sewing line
It is
a
to enhance the effect of the water wash.
Can you understand what I'm saying?
The hair line is a reflection of light and shadow
to achieve a wrinkled and bumpy effect.
Then we put all the parts that need the water to be washed
can be added to our sewing wrinkle.
You can check its effect in the window.
Since we have canceled a symmetry, so both sides have to be added.
It doesn't matter if you don't understand after watching it once.
You can watch it over and over again after watching the replay.
Then you will get used to it.
After you use all these materials, you can change the name for it.
It will be more convenient to find it.
Finally, I also made the waist wash texture for it.
The waist width is 40.
Change the width to 4 cm and use it on our waist.
Take a look at the water wash effect of the waist.
The color is a little too dark.
Reduce the transparency.
If you want to make it thinner,
we can add a water wash effect to the neckline.
Actually, I did not do it here.
Then I want to add water wash effect to my waist.
Okay, that's it.
Okay, so that was an explanation of the water washing effect of our printer.
Now let's talk about how to do a partial water wash.
First of all, there are two ways to do it.
The first way is to do it through a texture sticker.
In Claude's library, there are some preview effects.
In the Hardware and Trims folder, there is a Washing Texture.
We can also create some effects.
You can scan and add some texture to it.
Then save it as a PNG picture.
Make sure it's transparent.
Then add it in the way of a sticker.
We can't make holes with this method.
You can do it in the way of a sticker.
The second way is to apply the size of our pants to a texture separately.
In Photoshop, make a setting for the texture of the pants.
Then apply it to our pants.
You can make a hole in it.
Now let's take a look at how to do it.
First of all, let's do it in the way of a sticker.
Find our material.
This is our cat's nest folder.
There are many cat's nest water washing effects in it.
Right-click to add as a sticker.
Then put it on our pants.
After adding it, of course, we can adjust the position of this sticker.
You can adjust the position of this sticker in 2D and 3D.
Then shrink its size.
Then reduce its transparency.
You still have to look at it in our rendering.
Look at the 3D window.
It's very shallow.
But in the rendering, its shadow is still very deep.
So we can adjust its transparency according to the effect.
After you think it's OK.
We can paste this picture.
Copy it.
Paste the mirror on our symmetrical board.
If we use 6.2 at that time.
These two boards do not solve a symmetrical link.
We can directly copy it to the board of symmetrical modification.
Then its position is in a completely symmetrical state.
OK.
Now we paste the picture of this broken effect.
It's also our own in the library.
Directly load it in.
After adding it in.
It is also a adjustment to its size.
Then like this big one.
The effect of this matte white.
We can also use the sticker to do it.
Then I choose one.
Choose one.
Then here you can directly enter the size of our sticker.
Adjust it.
Rotate its direction.
Then change its transparency.
Directly changed to 5.
Then let's do this.
Now I will teach you how to use our one.
The board.
Wait a minute.
Let's look at our hole first.
Add it in.
It must be.
There is no way to penetrate.
One of the effects of the texture behind.
So we're going to use the second method we're talking about.
How to use the texture of the board.
using the texture of the board to create the effect of water washing and hole breaking.
First of all, let's copy the fabric of the jeans and give it a new name.
Then in the print mode, we can find this piece of fabric and make it wider.
We can make it a little narrower, so that we can create a picture.
We can make a comparison.
When we import it, we can adjust the preview to 1 to 1.
Then the resolution is based on the texture.
This texture was 144 dpi when I scanned it.
So I filled in 144 dpi in the resolution.
I recommend that you don't fill it too high.
If it's too high, the picture will be very large.
If each version is very large,
it will increase the resolution.
This file will be very large.
So the resolution is about 150 dpi.
It's almost OK.
Then we choose the outline of the board here.
Then display the picture.
Be sure to hook it up.
Then save this board.
2D quick photo is out.
It's actually quite far.
Then we refresh it.
Then add this picture to our fabric.
Then align its position.
Use our edit texture tool.
It's equivalent to our board.
It's applied to such a fabric.
Then we can use our PS.
Open our texture.
Give it some effects.
For example, I will create a shape.
Then fill in a white color on this shape.
Mix the color of this layer.
Adjust it to our stack.
Then select its filter.
A high silk blur.
The radius of the high silk blur can be adjusted a little larger.
Let it do this.
An effect of blurring white.
Then the color interface.
We put this.
Make it a little smaller.
Let it look a little darker.
Not so white.
Then we save this picture as our PNG.
Cover our original picture.
Remember to cover.
In this way, we can use one of our refresh.
Right click.
Refresh pattern.
Then this effect can be synchronized.
If we still want to make any adjustments.
We will directly adjust it in PS.
After adjusting it, we can refresh it directly.
Now we want to make this hole.
The texture of this hole.
The texture of the hole that was previously made.
Add it in.
Let's put the position down first.
Let's look at the position first.
Check it in the clone.
Okay, this position is a little low.
I want to make it a little higher.
Adjust it.
Select this layer.
Show the higher or lower layer.
And save it.
Then save it.
OK, this position is OK now.
Now I'm going to draw a draft.
Draw a draft, let's choose the bottom layer.
The best way to draw it is to remove the texture of the bottom layer.
Use the multi-ichten tool to directly select where we need to draw.
Delete the layer
and save it
It is still not transparent
This is because the texture on both sides of the fabric is different
So we need to also process the texture on the back
Because the texture on the back can only be seen in the 2D window
In the print mode, you can't see the texture on the back
So we can use the 2D window
You can see that the print mode is only a front-facing effect
If it is the back, we will use the 2D window to display the texture on the back
Save the file
Only this one is left
Only this one is left after re-selecting
Then the 2D photo will be displayed
Then open the saved image in the PS
And cut out the size
Ctrl-A, Ctrl-C, Ctrl-V
Paste it in this file
Align its position
We can see the hole here
And use this multi-faceted tool to select the necessary pixels
After removing the pixels, we will hide the other layers other than this layer
And then paste in the other layers of the image
Then save it as a PNG image
Cover it
Open the file we just saved
And apply the texture image on the back
After applying it, I found that it was still not transparent
It was still not transparent when rendering
Why is that?
This is because when we are doing the white-molding effect
Is there still a layer?
It was still not transparent because we did not decode it
So I went back to our PS
And found that layer
Yes, it is this layer
So we need to decode this layer
So when you decode it, remember not to miss it
I missed it at that time
In this way, there is no problem
Save it for later
Now we can see the effect of this hole
We can open it
Let's take a look
You can see the effect of the hole in the jeans
It's done
In fact, in the PS
I just made a hole
And a large-area mold
Including some of our cat's ears
Some small effects
You can do whatever you want to do with this water-washing effect
With the manual version, it will be more convenient
To draw some water-washing effects
You can use a stacker
And then adjust the high-definition blur
Okay, now let's do it
The effect of a fur edge of our jeans
So I put the fold-over edge of our bottom
The board is cut off
And then delete those boards
The effect of the fur edge
We first make a more regular fur edge
The regular fur edge
We made it through a thin small strip
We choose our bottom
Look at its length
Then create a board of the same length
Then the height is very thin
We are two millimeters
Then we copy another texture
Copy a fabric
Then apply it
After applying it
We sew it on the side of our pants
Then the particle diameter and the conflict thickness
Gently reduce it
Then add to the side
Okay, then give us the newly created
This piece of fabric
To apply a
A type of hair
Change its default hair type
Change it to our
Role-Age Denim
This is our
A preview of a fur edge of a jeans
Open our rendering
To see the effect of a hair rendering
Then we can adjust
Some parameters of hair
Make it more in line with
The effect we want
For example, we can
Make its thickness
Thickness
A little bigger
Then the chasing degree
Also a little bigger
Then the density can be adjusted
The density can be adjusted a little smaller
Then the color
We can go to the brush
And then
Add another light blue
About how to adjust the hair
We also had a master before
Live class
You can take a look at the previous course
I didn't talk about it in detail here
The method is anyway
Through a thin strip
Then set it to one
A attribute of a cowboy hair
To do
Then we take the
Same
Read slot
And then to the
Line of the
Layer
So
Then we'll
Do the
Version
Control
D
Let's sew it
As it is
We aren't
Connected
So
Let's take a look at the rendering, both corners are the result of the border.
This is a border with a rule, we can save this file.
The last one is the thinning effect, let's see how to do it.
The method is also very simple, it is also made by applying the texture of the border on a plate.
This is the texture of the border.
First, draw a plate, the width is the same width as it.
The height is about 5 cm.
Then sew it together.
Use the texture first.
The adjustment of our texture can be adjusted after fixing the proportion in the attribute editor.
Then it can see a little bit of that edge in the 3D window.
A hairy effect.
We can bend its edge.
Then adjust its height.
In this way, you can't see it.
Then sew it on the edge of our hair.
The sewing type is changed to Turned.
Select this plate and add it to the outside.
I will use it.
Then you can also make a new shape.
You can do it in this way.
How to make this shape of hair.
I will show you how to make this shape of hair.
Okay, now let's sum up the content of today's video on how to make a water-washed jeans.
First of all, we are going to make a pattern for our jeans.
First, we will scan the fabric from the food fabric.
Then we will choose a clothing with a larger area to scan our pattern.
Then we will make a continuous effect of it.
Both sides need to be made and generate a corresponding line drawing.
Then we also scan the water-washed effect of the edge.
Then process it into a two-sided continuous pattern effect.
Use our sewing and folding tools to add to our various edges.
Then some of these partial old-fashioned effects,
such as this hole, this kind of mold, and some of the partial molding, molding white.
Then we can make it through the method of pasting the picture or the pattern of the board.
Then the last edge, according to everyone's style,
if there is an edge,
you can use the pattern.
We will use the two methods we just taught to make our edge.
OK, so we have finished talking about the content of the jeans today.
If you have any questions, you can ask them.
We will talk about the items in 10 minutes if there are no questions.
We will first Q&A and then talk about the items.
Because the content of the items is not related to the jeans.
Just now someone said to adjust the color interface, right?
I remember.
The color interface is actually very simple.
Let's look for a pattern.
For example, this piece of cloth, let's open it in PS.
Then adjust the color interface in the image.
Then we go to the small triangle of the color interface.
Do you see that the color has become lighter?
This is lighter.
Make sure.
Then you can give him this picture.
Save it for him.
Use it as a light-colored jeans fabric.
Very simple.
How do the four sides do it in a row?
I won't talk about it today.
Because we talked about this content before.
Is there any other question?
I still want to know the color interface.
If the color interface is like this jeans fabric.
If it is a relatively flat jeans.
Then you can directly use our system to automatically generate a color interface.
If you want to make a color interface that has a stronger sense of encouragement.
You can use our PIXPLANT to generate a color interface.
For example, we have this pattern.
Are you done?
Then we are in this place.
Here.
Go to our one.
The pattern.
After adding it, you can generate a pattern here.
Make sure.
You don't have to care about this side.
Then the pattern is normal.
This is where it is.
This is one of his patterns.
The pattern is obviously too rough.
Then we can take it.
We can adjust its value.
Slightly adjust it for him.
Take this displacement range.
Smaller.
Just a little flat.
Did you see it?
Okay.
Just save this picture.
You can use this software.
In fact, it can also be used in PS.
But I use less PS.
This should also have.
There is a 3D.
Did you see it?
You can use it to generate a pattern.
You can also generate a pattern here.
Okay.
Any other questions?
Oh, you're talking about the F5?
The F5 feature has been around for a long time, it's not a new feature.
Does the setting layer also wear film? Is there any solution?
Well, this...
This needs to get the file to see what the specific situation is.
Generally speaking, after you set the layer,
I don't know if you set the conflict thickness...
If you set it to 0, it may still be a bit penetrated.
PS, do the detection operation.
PS, you have to download the filter 3D generation detection diagram.
It's right here.
And then you can see the parameters in it yourself.
It's below the filter, the 3D generation detection diagram.
How does the thick fabric show the thickness in the contact area?
Oh, I understand what you mean.
That is to say, you want to see...
Let's assume that this fabric is very thick.
There's this kind of thick effect here, right?
Well, because we removed the seam allowances in the 3D clothing production,
we sewed it directly to the board.
So what about the effect of the thickness?
We all go through one...
How about this? Let's open a default clothing.
The color of the jeans is too dark, I can't see it.
In this place, if you want to see an effect,
we can use our edit sewing line,
and then select this sewing line,
increase the strength of the line drawing,
and also increase the thickness of the line drawing.
And then...
Through this kind of shadow,
we can achieve the effect of this...
The effect of the screen.
I don't know if I have achieved the effect you want.
How to get the denim pattern we made this time?
We will put this material in the comments section of Bilibili,
and then you can click to download it,
or to enter certain keywords in our WeChat public number to get it.
Does the hair line need to be continuous?
Your text is already continuous,
so the hair line must be continuous.
Because your hair line is good,
因为你的发线图肯定是根据你的纹理去生成的。Because your hair line is definitely generated according to your texture.
用板片做的效果能走秀吗?用板片做的效果能走秀吗? Can the effect of using a board be stylish?
什么东西用板片做的效果啊?What is the effect of using a board?
你说复件吗?复件用板片做的效果,你可以粘在服装身上也可以走秀的啊。Can you say the effect of using a board? The effect of using a board can also be stylish even if you stick it on your clothes.
贴图会盖住线。贴图会盖住线。The sticker will cover the line. The sticker will cover the line.
那你试一下把贴图选中调整一下Z轴的间距呢。Then you try to select the sticker and adjust the distance of the Z-axis.
我们的贴图啊。Our stickers.
看一下。Let's see.
贴图。The stickers.
随便弄一张图做贴图吧。Let me just make a picture as a sticker.
这个啊。增加为贴图。This one. Increase as a sticker.
我们的贴图你选中之后,你可以在属性编辑器当中调整一个距Z轴的距离。After selecting the sticker, you can adjust the distance of the Z-axis in the parameter editor.
然后呢你可以输大一点啊。假设我输一个比较大的这5毫米吧。You can zoom in a little bit. Let's say I zoom in a little bit.
5毫米吧。可以看到我们这个贴图就飘起来了,看到没有。5mm. You can see that our sticker is floating.
所以说它如果盖住线了,你把那个值稍微调大一点试试看啊。So if it covers the line, you can try to increase the value a little bit.
默认是0.13,好像是。It seems to be 0.13.
印花排放想再听一下。印花排放是吧。印花排放就是在这里啊。And then you want to save the picture. Just click here to save the picture.
然后呢你要保存图片,就点一下这里有个保存图片。And then you want to save the picture. Just click here to save the picture.
然后呢把这个值预设改为我们的一个1比1。And then change this value preset to our 1 to 1.
1比1的话它就会根据你的这个面料幅宽。1 to 1, it will be based on the width of your fabric.
跟你用量比较高。It will be based on the width of your fabric.
你需要的这个长度去保存一张图片出来。You can save a picture with this length.
那这个分辨率大家可以去更改,手动的调整为你自己想要的一个值啊。建议就是150,差不多了啊。Then you can change the resolution to the value you want. The recommended value is about 150.
因为这个图片太大了,到时候运行起来也会比较慢一些。Because this picture is too big, it will run slower.
然后这个显示线段根据你的效果来,那因为我们不想要这些基础线啊什么线的,我们 Because we don't want these basic lines or anything, we
就可以把它去掉啊,反选掉。只保留我们的一个版片的外轮廓线。然后再保存就可以了。We can remove it and reverse it. It only keeps the outline of our board.
然后再保存就可以了。Then save it.
打印版片的话,放缝效果怎么弄?打印版片的话,放缝怎么弄啊?放缝看一下啊。打印版片的话,放缝怎么弄啊?放缝看一下啊。
放缝的话,打印版片的话,放缝看一下啊。放缝的话,
如果说你这个DXF指样上,如果说你这个DXF指样上,
本来就有毛边的,那你导进来的时候呢,我们来导一个啊,指样。然后我们导的时候啊,你把这个勾上,转换为缝缝。就是如果你指样上本来就有缝缝的话,你把这个勾上,勾上之后,你在那个指样上有缝缝了,它在硬化排放模式的时候就能够计算到你的缝缝量。那如果说你是在Clow里面做的一个板子,你要给它做一个缝缝。你把这个缝缝,就是如果你指样上本来就有缝缝的话,你把这个勾上,勾上之后,你在那个指样上有缝缝了,它在硬化排放模式的时候就能够计算到你的缝缝量。那如果说你是在C
加上缝缝,或者说你导板片的时候,你忘记勾那个选项了,那你可以在这个地方啊,有一个缝缝工具,可以选中它,然后框选我们的板片,去给这个板片一周加上缝缝。然后你也可以单击,就给这一个边啊,加缝缝。那缝缝的宽度你选中之后,可以在这边去改它的宽度啊,对吧。
那这样的话,你看我放好之后,在硬化排放模式下
这个缝缝的量就来了啊,我再重新初始化安排,看到没有。就能够计算进去啊,这个量。
还有什么问题吗?没有的话,我们就进入彩蛋环节了啊。好,我们来进入彩蛋环节。
彩蛋环节是我们很多用户想要看的一个放码啊,放码。
放码的话,我们首先呢,需要先创建一个放码组的信息。那在物体窗口这边,大家可以看到有一个放码栏。
单击一下我们的放码,然后在尺寸这个地方啊,点击一下增加。
增加我们的一个放码组,增加一个放码组,然后呢,我们选中我们的这个板片。
然后呢,应用我们的这一个放码组,这个地方的应用啊,应用于当前选定的这个板片啊。
好,它会提醒你AI曲线点将变为自由曲线点进行正确的放码。那这个什么意思呢?我们的曲线模式不是有一个AI曲线还有一个曲线点曲线吗?
那我们的放码的模式是在自由曲线点的一个模式下进行的,所以说它会转换一下啊,不用管它,点确定就行了。
好,然后呢,我们现在是只有一个码吧,那如果说你想要有几个码的话,你在这里啊,点击一下增加尺码。
假设有三个尺码啊,那你就再加两个,就是123就三个。
现在的话,我们放完码之后的这个板片呢,应用了放码信息的板片,它这个点啊,会变成这种绿色的一个状态,绿色的一个状态,就证明这个板片是应用了放码信息的。
那我们现在是选择了size1作为它的一个base啊,就是一个基础码。
那如果说你想要中间的这个码作为base的话,你可以切换到size2啊。
然后呢,我们用我们的这个编辑放码工具,编辑放码工具。
选中我们需要放码的点,比如说这个点。
然后呢,可以看到在属性编辑器当中会有一个间距和板片外线扩张,以及下面有一个箭头移动的距离。
那这三个我们一个一个来看,第一个呢是间距,间距是指我们第一个码,就是你有几个码,这边显示几个码啊,它在x轴跟y轴的一个距离,那这个是指两个码之间的一个距离。
这个是指我们。
用箭头去移动这个码数的时候的一个距离,那现在是10,也就是一公分,就是说我用这个小键盘的箭头向右移动一下,等一下啊,向右移动一下,看到没有,它现在就往我们的这一边偏移了一个值吧,所以说我们的第三个码,它就是这个,多了一公分啊,这边少了一公分,所以说在我们的间距的位置,size1它是比size2这个基码是多了一公分啊,所以说在我们的间距的位置,size1它是比size2这个基码是多了一公分啊,所以说在我们的间距的位置,size1它是比size2这个基码是多了一公分啊,所以说在我们的间距的位置,size1它是
是不是负10啊,这个是不是正10,那我们这个百变化性扩张是指两个码之间的一个间距,是不是就是10啊,明白哈,好,那如果说我们想要把这个放码的信息复制到其他的一个点的话,我们可以在这个点上右键复制,然后在这个点上右键粘贴,它就能够将这个点的放码信息复制到下一个点,那你也可以去框选我们的这个放码信息复制到下一个点,那你也可以去框选我们的这个放码信息复制到下一个点,那你也可以去框选我们的这个放码信息复制到下一个点,那你也可以去框选我们的这个放码信息复制到下一个点,那你也可以去框
and then press this little keyboard to put our code.
Okay, so this is one of our editor codes.
Okay, below the editor code, there is also an editor curve code.
Editor curve code is a code that can be used to put the position of our curve point.
For example, I click on the position of this curve point.
If I want to put a code on it, I can enter its value.
Let's say I change this place to an 8.
See, its keyframe has changed.
This tool is to change the value of the code that we put in this curve point.
Let me tell you about our new feature.
In our 6.2 new feature, there is a tool that can drag our point directly to put the code,
to put the code freely,
rather than inputting it.
Or it can only move the keyboard.
Okay, so this is our task for today,
about putting the code.
Do you have any questions?
How to pull out a beautiful and even wave?
A beautiful and even wave?
You mean you want to make that...
What is it called?
The effect of an extension board?
I am not sure if you are talking about the effect that I imagined.
We have a tool that can make an extension board,
and then it becomes a round-shaped t-shape.
And then you sew it on the edge,
and then you can make that round-shaped sun-lubric effect.
No, no, no.
No, what do you mean by that?
Pull out a beautiful and even wave.
This text information may not be very...
After the board is frozen,
will the metal eyes still run?
Will the metal eyes run away?
Are you talking about the gas eyes?
Are you talking about the gas eyes made with a button?
If you are talking about the gas eyes made with a button,
it is best to add them after the simulation is complete,
and then close the conflict,
and then stop the simulation.
Yes, we can.
This is a special problem for theay.
I think you have to read the document to know what is going on.
Reading the text is not so easy.
Not easy.
Can I change the hair to a model?
Sure, our model is in the file drawer of Avatar.
Find which model you are using,
find it in there.
Find hair.
There will be some hairstyles in it, you can change it, you can change it with a double machine, let's say I change it to a short hair like this
Can't you do the other parts of the simulation
The other parts of the simulation can be done
Oh, I got it, is it, is it the honeycomb, the wave I just said
Is it honeycomb
If you want to know how honeycomb works, you can go and follow our
The tips and tricks that Bilibili sent out, that little video
It should be
It should be soon, we should be making that video, and then we can go and watch that little video directly, and there will be a very detailed explanation
Is the master straight car course still going on
Uh, we're all planning our master straight car course right now
Wooden man, man, man, it's not true
Wooden
Wooden man, wooden man
Wooden man, this demand
Why do you use wooden man
Hey, do you know that we have a connected platform
Let's take a look
Promotion a wave
Wait a minute, I didn't count it well.
This is the network address.
From our official website, there is a family site at the bottom of the website.
Then find the Closet.
Then there is a Connect on the Closet side.
It's our kind of online mall.
Then there are a lot of our users,
global users,
to upload some of their 3D design works.
Then there is a competition.
The prizes will be on it.
Then, like you just said,
there is also this fabric,
there is also the material,
like this kind of bright film effect.
Then the model is below.
Then everyone can go and see.
If you need a model,
you can look for it here.
What?
When do you optimize the main page?
Our main page will have a major update next year.
You can look forward to it.
Any other questions?
If there are no questions,
then I'm going to end the broadcast.
Does the main page often have no content?
No.
This is the network I use now.
It's a normal network.
It's all there when you go in.
Do you still want to listen to it again?
Let's watch it again when we play it back.
I won't do it today.
Everyone has limited time.
I'll say one more sentence.
The place where the code is placed.
It's the clothing where we put the code.
Assume that
I can go here to check our code.
Display code.
Then,
I'll put this back too.
The back.
You can choose more.
I'll just choose it like this.
Then,
let's switch the code.
For example,
I switched to our third code.
Delete our name.
Delete the name.
Delete this too.
It may be a little bit of a problem.
Okay.
Let's switch to our third code.
Doesn't it get bigger?
After it gets bigger,
Sometimes it's with our model.
There may be some simulation.
There may be some problems.
In fact, we can go.
Use this automatically.
The translation will be automatically translated.
Then it can be automatically translated.
This is also one of our.
A better one.
A useful function.
I'll show you.
You can change the size of this model.
Then use this to automatically translate.
The display of the cloud set is now only able to display the lowest quality picture.
If you want to display high-quality pictures,
It is a charging function.
The face of the model is not very good.
This is a difference in the aesthetic.
Maybe it is.
We will also respond to this question.
Now we have a new hairstyle. Let me take a look at it.
I just did it.
This should be more suitable for black models.
Pretty cool.
An explosion head.
Okay, what other questions do you have?
If there are no questions, we will end the broadcast.
How to connect to PS?
We have a way to open this place in the text.
There is an add application here.
If you don't have it, there are only these two buttons.
Just click on this add.
Then you find the location of the program you installed.
For example, Adobe.
Then PS.
Then you find the ES1 file of PS.
Then open it.
Very good.
Very simple.
Okay.
That's all for today.
See you next time.
Bye bye.
I don't think there are any more questions.